https://bridgewater.church/privacy-policy

Stories
Bridgewater Privacy PolicyThis website or mobile application (each referred to as the “Site”) is brought to you (“you” or “user”) by Bridgewater Church (“we”, “us”, or “Bridgewater”). This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal and non-personal information we collect on the Site, how we use such information and to whom and under what circumstances we may disclose it. By using the Site, you agree to the collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information (defined below) as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.Personal InformationWe only collect Personal Information from you when you: (1) order products and/or services; (2) contact us via email or other means; (3) submit information related to a ministry or ministry service in which you participate, volunteer, or seek information about; or (4) otherwise provide us with your personal information. Personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) we collect may include, without limitation, your name, age, email address, phone number, mailing address, username, password, credit card information, place of employment, and church affiliation, if you submit such information. We may require certain pieces of this information in order to create and maintain a personal account for you or on your behalf. A personal account may be required to enable you to access certain services, ministry environments, or other non-public areas of the Site, or purchase products and services on or through the Site. We may request additional information to verify your identity in certain instances. We may use cookies and other available technology to remember your preferences and customized settings, facilitate access to the Site, and verify access to personal accounts.Non-Personal InformationVisitors are not required to register with Bridgewater to access the public pages of the Site. However, as part of the standard operation of the Site, Bridgewater or its third party contractor may collect certain non-personal information from you, including but not limited to your browser type, mobile device type, operating system, IP address and the domain name from which you accessed the Site. This information is not personally identifiable and is only used in aggregate (not in any way that personally identifies you). In addition, we may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visit the Site, the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the Site, the number of times you return to the Site and other click-stream data.Bridgewater may use Google Analytics to generate and view reports regarding demographics and interest in the Site. If you would like to opt out, please install an appropriate web browser plugin, extension, or add-on.CookiesWe may use cookies to collect the non-personal information described above. A cookie is a small text file that may be stored on your browser cache or mobile device for record-keeping purposes. We may also use cookies to: (1) monitor Site usage; (2) provide you with customized content and advertising; and (3) conduct research to improve our content and services. You may change your web browser’s settings to adjust your cookie preferences. Please be aware that if you reject or block all cookies you may not be able to use certain features of the Site or take advantage of all our offerings.Accessing Your InformationYou may access Personal Information you provide to us, or correct or modify such Personal Information, or direct us not to disclose your Personal Information to any third party other than those necessary to complete a transaction you initiate on the Site, those related to a legal proceedings, or those related to a change in control of Bridgewater or certain of its assets. To do so, please send an email with your request to office@bwater.org.How We Use Your InformationWe may use the Personal Information and non-personal information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: (1) to fulfill your requests for products and services; (2) to assist Bridgewater serving you related to a certain ministry service in which you or your child participates; (3) to organize volunteers for particular ministry purposes; (4) to contact you when necessary; (5) to review and analyze Site usage and operations; (6) to address problems with the Site, our ministry, or our products and services; and (7) to protect the security or integrity of the Site and our ministry; and (8) to provide you with targeted events and/or advertising on the Site.Disclosure of InformationWe may transfer or otherwise disclose Personal Information and non-personal information collected from and about you to the following entities for the following purposes: (1) to our employees, independent contractors, subsidiaries, affiliates, consultants, ministry partners, service providers and suppliers, if the disclosure will enable any of these entities to perform a business, professional, fulfillment, marketing, information technology, or technical support function for us; (2) to our employees, independent contractors, service providers and suppliers, to fulfill a product or service request; (3) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of the Site Terms of Use (if applicable) or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (4) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; (5) to an entity within the Bridgewater family of churches and ministries including their related ministry environments; and (5) in the event that ownership or control of Bridgewater or a portion of our organization changes by transfer, or a portion of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets.Internet CommunicationThe privacy of communication over the Internet cannot be guaranteed, because the Internet is not a secure medium. You agree that Bridgewater is not responsible for any harm, loss, or damage you may incur by the sending of personal or confidential information over the Internet by or to Bridgewater.Children’s PrivacyWe are committed to complying with the guidelines set forth by the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act.  The Site is not directed to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. If you are the parent or guardian of a child age 13 or under who has provided us with Personal Information and you would like that information removed, please contact us at office@bwater.org.Third Party ApplicationsYou may be able to access the Site or sign into your personal account through a third party application (e.g. Facebook). In allowing access through such an application, we may receive certain information (including Personal Information) from the third party application and disclose certain information to such third party application. If you access the Site or your account from a mobile application, you may provide us with geo-location details. You may prevent this disclosure by adjust the settings on your mobile device.Third Party SitesThis Privacy Policy applies only to the Site. Other websites Bridgewater owns and websites owned or operated by third parties may contain different privacy policies and practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other person, entity, organization, or website to or from which the Site links or is linked. Users are strongly encouraged to read and regularly review posted privacy policies on all websites, whether or not owned by us or affiliated with the site.Changes to Privacy PolicyWe reserve the right to modify the Privacy Policy from time to time, with or without cause or prior notice. We will post all changes to the Privacy Policy on the Site. Changes to the Privacy Policy are effective immediately upon posting. Users are responsible for reviewing the Privacy Policy regularly. Use of the Site indicates User’s full and complete agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Use of information (including Personal Information) we gather or that is in our possession is subject to the Privacy Policy as in effect at the time of use.Governing LawThis Privacy Policy and its terms shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Pennsylvania without regard to the conflicts of laws provisions therein.Your California Privacy RightsUnder California’s "Shine the Light" law, California residents who provide Personal Information in obtaining products or services for personal, family, or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us once a calendar year information about the Personal Information we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of Personal Information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared Personal Information for the immediately prior calendar year (e.g., requests made in 2016 will receive information regarding 2015 sharing activities).To obtain this information from Bridgewater, please send an email message to office@bwater.org with "Request for California Privacy Information" on the subject line and in the body of your message. The requested information, if required by law, will be provided to you at your email inbox.Other: Pushpay Privacy PolicyCCB Privacy Policy Effective Date: July 22, 2019
